Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Video and Film Works, 1975-2015; 79.9 Linear Feet in 42 cassette boxes, 36 record cartons, 8 manuscript boxes, 4 LP boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 2 flat files; 195 VHS; 133 U-matic; 111 Hi8; 85 audiocassettes; 70 MiniDV; 14 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 6 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 4 1_Inch_Video_Reel
  - Subseries II.D: Works by Date, 1975-2015
    - 30 Seconds, 1983
      - Tom Kay Camera Master, August 20, 1983 (Box 110, 1 inch video reel 437_2267)
      - Tom Kay Part 1, August 23, 1983 (Box 126, U-matic 437_1495)
      - Danceteria, October 4, 1983 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1640)
      - Tom Kay Danceteria, Tape #1 Camera Master, October 4, 1983 (Box 110, 1 inch video reel 437_2266)
      - Tom Kay Danceteria, Tape #2 Camera Master, October 4, 1983 (Box 111, 1 inch video reel 437_2269)
      - Tom Kay Danceteria, Tape #1, October 4-6, 1983 (Box 139, U-matic 437_1874)
      - Danceteria, undated (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0713)
      - Demo, ARZ Productions, undated (Box 128, U-matic 437_1602)
      - Tom Kay Danceteria, Tape #2, October 4-6, 1983 (Box 139, U-matic 437_1875)
    - Compilation Tape -- Belize, 30 Seconds, Cable TV, 4 XAMPL Performance, 1983 (Box 138, Vhs 437_1841)
    - "Super - 8 oder 9 - Filme", circa 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, 1983-1984
      This documentary depicts Branca's orchestra on their European tour, and was shown at film festivals throughout Europe and the USA.
      - Audio, 1983 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0781)
      - On Tour, 1983-1984 (Box 124, U-matic 437_1564)
      - Vienna, May 8, 1983 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0779)
      - Zeche in Bochum, New Movement #1, May 18, 1983 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0151)
      - Trax for Branca tape, Connie and A, December 12, 1983 - January 15, 1984 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0708)
      - Branca for the movie, December 22, 1983 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0785)
      - Branca for the movie, 2-track mix, December 22, 1983 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0778)
      - Glenn Branca at the Ritz, December 23, 1983 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1620)
      - Production File, 1983 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - #1, 1984 (Box 126, U-matic 437_1497)
      - Branca at City, 1984 (Box 124, U-matic 437_1561)
      - Master, 1984 (Box 140, U-matic 437_1880)
      - Master, 1984 (Box 153, U-matic 437_0048)
      - Video, 1984 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1484)
      - Notes, master slides, 1984 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1172)
      - Original soundtrack, 1984 (Box 125, U-matic 437_1233)
      - Video, 1984 (Box 153, U-matic 437_0049)
      - Video, 1984 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1593)
      - Zatar, undated (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0756)
    - Compilation Tape -- 30 Seconds, Sun Diary, 1983-1985 (Box 145, U-matic 437_2170)
    - Compilation Tape -- It's a Live Laser, 30 Seconds, 1983-1985 (Box 141, U-matic 437_1885)
    - Repertoire of Phoebe Legere -- Release Form, March 18, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Compilation Tape -- 4 XAMPL, A-Z Original rough edit, April 9, 1984 (Box 133, U-matic 437_1686)
    - "ABC (B) NYC" -- Work in progress, August, 1984 (Box 140, U-matic 437_1879)
    - A-Z Film Proposal, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - The Date, Caterina Borelli, 1984 (Box 140, U-matic 437_1883)
    - Xero Proposal, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Compilation Tape -- It's a Live Laser, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, AEIOU, 1984-1985 (Box 140, Vhs 437_1866)
    - Compilation Tape -- It's a Live Laser, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, AEIOU, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1131)
    - Compilation Tape -- ID / It's Dance, It's a Live Laser, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, AEIOU, 1984-1985 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1623)
    - Compilation Tape -- ID / It's Dance, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, It's a Live Laser sample, 1984-1987 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1644)
    - Compilation Tape -- Glenn Branca Symphony #4 / Physics, ID / It's Dance, 1984-1988 (Box 140, Vhs 437_1855)
    - Compilation Tape -- "Samples / Paint 8mm", 1984-1990 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1768)
    - Compilation Tapes -- "Excerpts from finished works", 1984-1990
      - Video (Box 138, Vhs 437_1833)
      - Video (Box 120, Vhs 437_1202)
      - Video (Box 130, Vhs 437_1635)
    - Compilation Tape -- Video selects, 1984-1992 (Box 138, Vhs 437_1846)
    - Shot Logs and Audio / Video Inserts, 1984 - 2007 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Elves + A 4M Edit, April 1, 1985 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0051)
    - Compilation Tape -- Ken Hiratsuka, Tubular Bells, ABC, It's a Live Laser, April 8-17, 1985 (Box 77, Audiocassette 437_0560)
    - "An Evening of Poetry Video" -- St. Marks Poetry Project and Colab TV, May 26, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "Alternating Currents" Video Exhibition, June 15 - July 6, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16, Box Shared Fales 116, Folder 20)
    - Compilation Tape -- ID / It's Dance, It's a Live Laser, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, 1985 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1652)
    - Compilation Tape -- It's a Live Laser, excerpts of Eye and MoMA, 1985 (Box 124, U-matic 437_1553)
    - Sun Diary, 1985
      - #1, June, 1985 (Box 156, Betamax 437_1905)
      - #1 (Box 140, U-matic 437_1884)
      - #2 (Box 124, Betamax 437_1397)
      - #3 (Box 141, Betamax 437_1907)
    - New York Film Festival Downtown, circa 1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Compilation Tape -- "Excerpts of two works", 1985-1986 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1590)
    - It's Dance, Laser A-Z, 1985-1987; FA_MSS_437_ER_20
    - Michael Castner, May 6, 1986 (Box 153, U-matic 437_0050)
    - Susan Britton, Willoughby raw material, May 11, 1986 (Box 124, U-matic 437_1225)
    - "Remote Faces: Outerpretation" Video Installation, October 2, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - #14, Michael Castner, circa 1986 (Box 124, U-matic 437_1398)
    - Audio for film, 1986 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0754)
    - Compilation Tape -- Excerpts of Opera, Laser Work, ID / It's Dance, 1986 (Box 138, Vhs 437_1850)
    - Compilation Tape -- Super 8 and 16, dub of Austria work, Laser, 1986 (Box 142, U-matic 437_2119)
    - "N.Y. Video Night" Screening Poster, Münster, 1986 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Teleopera -- Kitchen edit, 1986 (Box 129, U-matic 437_1608)
    - Water Sculpture -- TV Edit, 1986 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1175)
    - Mirror Letters, Animation, 1986-1987 (Box 138, Vhs 437_1842)
    - AEIOU, 1986-1988
      - Original material, Austria, 1986 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1619)
      - Video, August 10, 1987 (Box 132, U-matic 437_1670)
      - Reel Mixes, May 27, 1988 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0855)
      - Adazee Building Blox, Intro, undated (Box 131, U-matic 437_1674)
      - Color mix with effects, undated (Box 153, U-matic 437_2423)
      - Computer graphics, undated (Box 156, U-matic 437_1669)
      - Excerpts, undated (Box 126, U-matic 437_1498)
      - Music, undated (Box 123, U-matic 437_1223)
      - Video, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1168)
      - Video, undated (Box 129, U-matic 437_1606)
      - Video, undated (Box 129, U-matic 437_1613)
      - Video, undated (Box 131, U-matic 437_1678)
    - Videonale, 1986 - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - AU, 1987; FA_MSS_437_ER_21
    - Cast Iron TV, 1987
      - "Hello, Hello, Austria", undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1124)
      - Live recording (Box 128, Vhs 437_1583)
      - Video (Box 120, Vhs 437_1218)
    - Compilation Tape -- ID / It's Dance Original edit, Performance excerpts, Raw laser material, 1987 (Box 138, Vhs 437_1847)
    - Compilation Tape -- It's a Live Laser, ID / It's Dance, 1987 (Box 156, U-matic 437_1894)
    - NYFA - Artist in residence program, 1987 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1646)
    - "Peace on Earth" Graphics, 1987 (Box 140, Vhs 437_1858)
    - "Soul to Soul" Teleconferencing Network, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "Techno Bop" Show, The Kitchen, March, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - TVA, Center for Media Arts, 1987 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1628)
    - "Video Playhouse," Chicago, October, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - ID / It's Dance, 1987-1989
      - Music, April, 1987 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0662)
      - Dub from master, November 11, 1987 (Box 142, U-matic 437_1898)
      - Master clip reel, theme, voiceover intro, November 11, 1987 (Box 132, U-matic 437_1675)
      - Lyrics, melody, vocals, 1987 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0675)
      - Theme song music by Eric Ambel, 1987 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0171)
      - Production File, 1987 - 1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - "Letter from Marbles," Show #7 edits, January - March 12, 1988 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1654)
      - "In the Snow", January, 1988 (Box 89, Hi8 437_1243)
      - ID / It's Dance, January 30 - February 2, 1988 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1649)
      - Advert #4, February 20, 1988. (Box 130, Vhs 437_1647)
      - Eric Ambel, The Hound, May 13, 1989 (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0480)
      - "The Love Song", undated (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0661)
      - Copies from original, undated (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0655)
      - Demo, undated (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0664)
      - Master intro, undated (Box 126, U-matic 437_1499)
      - Show #111, Theme with Tricia voiceover, undated (Box 124, U-matic 437_1503)
      - Theme song, excerpts and credits, undated (Box 129, U-matic 437_1610)
      - Theme song, lyrics, vocals, undated (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0481)
      - Video Samples, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1845)
      - Body Shop Master Dub Combo, undated (Box 156, U-matic 437_1895)
    - Grant Applications, 1987 - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Eat Your Words / Letter by Letter Proposal, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Laser Opera Proposal, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Made in 8 Video Equipment Loan Program, 1988 - 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sun Daze Away, 1988-1992
      This travelogue montage across America's southwest was sponsored by Cannon Corp. and the 8mm Video Council. It premiered at the Central Park Summer Stage and was distributed by the Kitchen.
      - Video, 1988 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1638)
      - Axiom Productions, 1988 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1592)
      - Video, May 27-30, 1988 (Box 82, Hi8 437_2261)
      - Rough Edit, Kitchen #20/19, October 20, 1988 (Box 103, Hi8 437_2185)
      - Tape No. 5, Kitchen edit, November 17, 1988 (Box 103, Hi8 437_2202)
      - Electronic Records, 1989; FA_MSS_437_ER_22
      - Video, 1989 (Box 137, Vhs 437_1778)
      - Eyewitness, 1989-1992 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1142)
      - Five shorts aired on Nickelodeon, 1989 (Box 140, Vhs 437_1856)
      - EYW, soundtrack, February 10, 1989 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0858)
      - Video installation, March, 1990 (Box 119, U-matic 437_1119)
      - Distribution Agreement, June 25, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Hound at Brownies, August 14, 1990 (Box 103, Hi8 437_2204)
      - Screening ephemera, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Demo, 1991 (Box 121, U-matic 437_1122)
      - After Dance, K edit no. 6, Letters Nik, undated (Box 84, Hi8 437_2264)
      - Credits, Travel footage, A Cameo, Kids, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1123)
      - Go Back to Frankie Fare, Girl Animated, undated (Box 153, U-matic 437_0044)
      - Last tape in Florida, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2205)
      - Purple sky, undated (Box 157, Hi8 437_2262)
      - Rough Edit, Kitchen No. 4, undated (Box 79, Hi8 437_2257)
      - Rough Edit #2, Kitchen tape #6, 7, 5, 12, 9, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2199)
      - Rough Edit #3, Kitchen tape #8, 9, 14, 17, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2201)
      - Yosemite, undated (Box 81, Hi8 437_2258)
      - Video, undated (Box 115, Vhs 437_1179)
      - Video, undated (Box 131, U-matic 437_1677)
      - Video, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1835)
      - Video, undated (Box 81, Hi8 437_2259)
      - Video, undated (Box 81, Hi8 437_2260)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sun Daze Away, Eat Your Words, Marbles, and Sculpture Garden, 1989 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1180)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sun Daze Away, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, It's a Live Laser, 1989 (Box 116, U-matic 437_1083)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sun Daze Away, New York States, 1989-1992 (Box 116, U-matic 437_1082)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sun Daze Away, Connie wedding, Peter Pan, Leon in Alphabet piece, 1989 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1043)
    - Compilation Tape -- Arleen Schloss Logo, AU, Sun Daze Away, 1989 (Box 131, U-matic 437_1664)
    - Eureeka's Castle, 1989-1990
      - Bluebird (Box 135, Vhs 437_1702)
      - D'am Bones (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0863)
      - Live action segments (Box 119, U-matic 437_1116)
      - Video vignettes (Box 120, Vhs 437_1195)
    - Nickelodeon, 1989-1990
      - Rainbow, letters, paint, June 20, 1989 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1278)
      - Production File, 1989 - 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Video, 1989-1991 (Box 94, Minidv 437_1408)
      - Miami, July 22-24, 1990 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1309)
      - Video, undated (Box 128, Vhs 437_1600)
      - Video, undated (Box 114, Vhs 437_1034)
    - Demo Reels, 1989-1991
      - Demo, 1989 (Box 140, Vhs 437_1871)
      - Demo Reel, 1989 (Box 137, Vhs 437_1779)
      - Demo Reel, 1989 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1648)
      - Demo -- Fashion, 1990 (Box 143, Vhs 437_1931)
      - Demo Reel, 1991 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1703)
      - Demo Reel, undated (Box 130, Vhs 437_1625)
      - Demo Reel #2, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1208)
    - Compilation Tape -- New York States, Sun Daze Away, Democratic Convention, 1989-1992 (Box 118, U-matic 437_1109)
    - Audio samples, 1989-1998
      - "World Sounds", 1989 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0827)
      - "Exotic Sounds for A", January, 1998 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0067)
      - "Exotic Sounds", January, 1998 (Box 84, Dat 437_0797)
      - "Africa / Mora", undated (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0883)
      - "Africa / Mora", undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0369)
      - "Amazon Jungle from Connie Bob", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0054)
      - "Animal Sounds, Sound Effects Libraries", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0062)
      - "Exotic Sounds", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0066)
      - "Exotic Sounds", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0070)
      - "Exotic Sounds", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0072)
      - "Exotic Sounds", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0086)
      - "Exotic Sounds", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0090)
      - "Sound Effects", undated (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0780)
    - Harvestworks Residencies, 1989 - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Video Production -- Resources and Outreach, 1989 - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Kitchen Video Annex -- Correspondence and Ephemera, 1989 - 2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Film Screening Flyers, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - RESTRICTED: Compilation Tape -- Sun Daze Away, Rivington School at PS 1, circa early 1990s (Box 137, Vhs 437_1782)
    - Jane Johnston Excerpts, circa 1990s (Box 122, Vhs 437_1151)
    - Nik's Davidson Norris, Nik Williams Marbel, circa 1990s (Box 137, Vhs 437_1802)
    - "Video Toons!" Screenings, DCTV, circa 1990s (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Squat Theatre Promo Tape, February, 1990 (Box 119, U-matic 437_1111)
    - "Video Art" Exhibition, University of Rhode Island, March 27-April 13, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11, Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Nik Shorts, Edits, June 28, 1990 (Box 125, U-matic 437_1230)
    - "Video Drive-In: The Alternative Voice," Central Park Summerstage, August 14 - 15, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8, 12, Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Cast Iron TV Spring Series Broadcast, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Compilation Tape -- Hi tek-teens, Sidewalks of NY, Graphics, Eye, Dumpster, Tompkins Square, 1990 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1143)
    - "Glass Eyes" -- Computer stuff, work in progress, 1990 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1744)
    - Nickelodeon, circa 1990; FA_MSS_437_ER_23
    - TV Abende Amerikanischer Videokunst, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Compilation Tape -- From Kepler 2 Cyberspace: Virtual Worlds / Digital Dreams, Art Around the Park, 1990-1993 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1596)
    - From Kepler 2 Cyberspace: Virtual Worlds / Digital Dreams, 1990-1993
      This is a documentary on the pioneers of virtual reality.
      - "Sample Tape of Proposed Project", 1990 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1911)
      - Performance #7, September 7, 1990 (Box 74, Hi8 437_2249)
      - Video, 1990-1993 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1909)
      - Video, 1990-1993 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1910)
      - Video, 1990-1993 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1908)
      - Video, 1993 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1594)
      - Video, 1993 (Box 119, U-matic 437_1110)
      - Video, 1993 (Box 139, U-matic 437_1828)
      - Master, 1993 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2073)
      - PS 19 After School Program, 1993 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0989)
      - Video, June, 1993 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1971)
      - Production File, 1993 - 1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Electronic Records, 1994; FA_MSS_437_ER_27
      - End, Minksky, "Eye" Piece, Ben Britton, undated (Box 77, Hi8 437_2253)
    - Video Equipment Loans -- Agreements and Correspondence, 1990 - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts -- Video Fellowship and Grant Materials, 1990 - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Full Moon Killer -- Master, edit, January 28, 1991 (Box 134, U-matic 437_1824)
    - "Eye," Yeohlee and Arleen, April, 1991 (Box 89, Hi8 437_1245)
    - "Old and New Masters of Super-8" Festival, Anthology Film Archives, April 12 - 14, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Workshop piece, raw material on Chance and Aging, August, 1991 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1727)
    - Compilation Tape -- Hi tek teens, Tompkins Square rough pieces, 1991 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1154)
    - Raw material, 1991 (Box 134, U-matic 437_1827)
    - Studio A, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 44, Box 13, Folder 9, Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Wall Street with steadycam, 1991 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1296)
    - Across street / Nik, January, 1992 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1299)
    - "The Best of the Worst", January, 1992 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1149)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sarl Deies, AIR Gallery, Interviews, March 31, 1992 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1155)
    - Compilation Tape -- New York States, A Day in the Life of PS 19, Chance to Succeed, circa 1992 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2070)
    - Democratic Convention, New York City, 1992
      - Interviews, rough edit (Box 138, U-matic 437_1831)
      - Video (Box 122, Vhs 437_1128)
    - Election Special, 1992
      - Revised Master (Box 138, U-matic 437_1830)
      - Video (Box 141, Vhs 437_1914)
    - "Video Witness 3: Networking in the 90s!" Festival, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - New York States, 1992-1995
      - Video, 1992 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2030)
      - Video, 1992 (Box 137, Vhs 437_1796)
      - "Claire's", 1995 (Box 92, Hi8 437_1330)
      - Master, undated (Box 98, Hi8 437_1995)
    - Video Production -- Invoices, 1992 - 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3, 4)
    - "Full moon, Dumpster, Police, Cabbages", April - May, 1993 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1362)
    - Cable TV, 1993 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1148)
    - Compilation Tape -- "Last piece - China," Art Around the Park, Virtual Worlds/Digital Dreams, John Cage Interview, 1993 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1630)
    - Compilation Tape -- From Kepler 2 Cyberspace: Virtual Worlds / Digital Dreams, Art Around the Park, 1993 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1710)
    - Montage 93 Video -- Proposal, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - St. Patrick's Day Protests, Arrests, 1993 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1696)
    - "Writers on Writers: Demonstration Video", 1993 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1071)
    - X, 1993-1994
      - "Outside Window Gerddah", 1993 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1743)
      - Berlin, Bremen, January, 1994 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1585)
      - Electronic Records, circa 1994; FA_MSS_437_ER_28
      - Berlin, Bremen, undated (Box 131, Vhs 437_1699)
      - Video, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1132)
    - "The First Language, Babel," Gorbachov Ch. 13, December 27, 1994 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1759)
    - The Change -- Proposal, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - New York International Video Festival, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Retrospective, 1994 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1595)
    - Compilation Tape, 1995 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1522)
    - Yeohlee TV, 1995 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1762)
    - News, TV Ads, September 12, 1996 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2144)
    - "Old and New Masters of Super-8," Austria Filmmakers Cooperative, November, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Compilation Tape -- Branca, The Making of Super 8 A-Z New York, Smoke, March, 1997 (Box 127, U-matic 437_1560)
    - Bronx Zoo, July 12, 1997 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1983)
    - Museum of Modern Art -- Film Release Form, October 28, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Botanical Garden and Aquarium, December 31, 1997 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1728)
    - U R Beauty, 1997-1999
      - #2, Shu Uemura, December 16, 1997 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1009)
      - #3A, December 18-23, 1997 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1019)
      - "Aquarium", December 31, 1997 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1008)
      - "Closeups", December 23, 1997 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1021)
      - Arleen, December 29, 1996 - January 19, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0974)
      - Carlton, December 29, 1997 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1016)
      - Production File, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - #13A, #13B, Carlton, January 7, 1998 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1018)
      - #14, January 7, 1998 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1020)
      - "ZA", January 7, 1998 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1007)
      - Poetry, Shu Uemura, January 12, 1998 (Box 133, U-matic 437_1685)
      - Long #2 Catalog Model Shots, January 14, 1998 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1006)
      - Beta #2, Sweden, 1999 (Box 143, Vhs 437_2137)
      - #15, Carlton, Soho, January 7, 1999 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1017)
      - #1, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1726)
      - #3, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1488)
      - #10, Sculpture Garden Exercise, undated (Box 144, Vhs 437_2138)
      - Alison, #7, 60, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1752)
      - "Shi X", undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0316)
    - Product Shot, January 7, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0975)
    - Climbing the Gold Mountain, April, 1998
      - Video, April 24, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0967)
      - Video, April 25, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0969)
      - Video, undated (Box 88, Minidv 437_0968)
    - Nina Kuo China 2000, December 16-17, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0984)
    - 30 Years in 30 Minutes -- Production File, 1998 - 2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Demonstration, Roosevelt Park, February, 1999 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1013)
    - Dalai Lama, 1999 (Box 143, Vhs 437_2134)
    - Special Collaboration -- Victor-Victor Films, Suisse-Marocaine, 1999-2001 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1589)
    - Video Production -- Equipment Receipts, 1999 - 2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Computer video with Lettie and Kevin, April 2000 (Box 95, Minidv 437_1445)
    - Bird, January, 2001 (Box 80, Minidv 437_2288)
    - Remembrance, September 11, 2001 (Box 122, Vhs 437_1159)
    - Art 21st Century, PBS, January 30, 2002 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1736)
    - Inscapes, Lorin Roser, 2002 (Box 120, Vhs 437_1198)
    - "Procore", 2005 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1547)
    - DADA Dada -- A's Camera, March 25, 2006 (Box 95, Minidv 437_1442)
    - Kathy Acker Documentary Project -- License Agreement, November 29, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Amy Arbus Documentary -- Release Form, February 7, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Film Screening at the New Museum, October 16, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - "Within Zero: White Box Salutes John Cage", December 9-23, 2012 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Anthology Film Archives Deed of Gift, 2015 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 1 Hour Video Show -- World Premier, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - ABC, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1532)
    - Aging, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1775)
    - Alison / Notations, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1750)
    - Another Day and Buster N.K., undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1483)
    - AU -- Hound, undated (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0657)
    - Barbara tapes, undated (Box 89, Minidv 437_1022)
    - "Better Yet!" Film Screening, Stilwende, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Compilation Tape -- "Best shorts", undated (Box 139, U-matic 437_1873)
    - Compilation Tape -- "Excepts of works", undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1749)
    - Compilation Tape -- "Finished works for Rockefeller", undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1718)